/// success : true
/// data : {"attempt":{"attempt_id":726,"student_id":2,"started_at":"20:56:10"},"quiz":{"id":25,"title":"امتحان المحاضره السادسة (Comprehension)","description":"<div class=\"exam-alert\">\r\n<h3>❗ تنبيهات مهمة:</h3>\r\n<ul>\r\n<li>لا تقم بتحديث الصفحة أو إغلاقها أثناء أداء الامتحان، لأن هذا قد يؤدي إلى فقدان إجاباتك أو إنهاء المحاولة تلقائيًا.</li>\r\n<li>سيتم إغلاق الامتحان تلقائيًا بعد انتهاء الوقت المحدد، ولن تتمكن من إرسال إجاباتك بعد ذلك.</li>\r\n<li>لا تستخدم أكثر من جهاز أو أكثر من نافذة/لسان (Tab) للامتحان، فقد يؤدي ذلك إلى فقدان البيانات أو حظر المحاولة.</li>\r\n<li>تأكد من أن اتصال الإنترنت مستقر قبل البدء.</li>\r\n<li>بعد الضغط على زر \"إرسال\"، لا تغادر الصفحة حتى تظهر لك رسالة التأكيد بنجاح إرسال الامتحان.</li>\r\n<li>في حالة وجود مشكلة تقنية أثناء الامتحان، يرجى التواصل فورًا مع الدعم الفني.</li>\r\n</ul>\r\n</div>","course_id":4,"have_duration":true,"duration_minutes":16,"attempt_count":100,"remaining_attempts":76,"full_score":16,"question_count":8,"questions":[{"type":"reading_passage","id":3,"description":"<p class=\"MsoNormal\" style=\"margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; line-height: 15.6933px; font-size: 11pt; font-family: Calibri, sans-serif; text-align: center;\" align=\"center\"><strong><u><span dir=\"RTL\" lang=\"AR-SA\" style=\"font-size: 18pt; line-height: 25.68px; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif;\">&nbsp;</span></u></strong></p>\r\n<p class=\"MsoNormal\" style=\"margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; line-height: 15.6933px; font-size: 11pt; font-family: Calibri, sans-serif;\"><strong><span style=\"font-size: 14pt; line-height: 19.9733px; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif;\">Read the following passage, then answer the questions: Today, in most industrialized countries in the world, buildings are designed to withstand various, unexpected natural disasters. Safety measures are installed in modern-day designs to help contain the spread of fire, and design engineers make sure newer structures are deliberately planned to hold against the violent shifting of the earth during an unexpected earthquake. However, such deliberate design and planning was not the case during the early 1900s. On April 18, 1906, in the morning hours of the day, the citizens of San Francisco, California, were witnesses to an earthquake so monumental. The tremors were felt as far north as Oregon. Neither the city nor its people were prepared for what would happen next: the devastation of their city. The actual earthquake only lasted two minutes. Of course, the violent tremors must have seemed much longer to the actual eyewitnesses, but the fires that came after the earthquake lasted for nearly three days. The enormous loss from the disaster included the lives of at least five hundred people, and an estimated three thousand acres of the city were destroyed. This disaster is often called simply the \"Great Quake\" because of the vast destruction that occurred.</span></strong></p>","questions":[{"id":283,"quiz_id":25,"question":"1. The best sentence that can summarize the last paragraph is...........................","answers":[{"id":1205,"answer":"a. The kinds of earthquakes that happened in San Francisco"},{"id":1206,"answer":"b. The duration and the effects of San Francisco earthquake"},{"id":1207,"answer":"c. The preparation the citizens of San Francisco made to face the earthquake"},{"id":1208,"answer":"d. The government stands with its citizens together to encounter the earthquake."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":284,"quiz_id":25,"question":"2. The best title for the passage is...............","answers":[{"id":1209,"answer":"a. New buildings can face natural disasters"},{"id":1210,"answer":"b. New buildings are designed by natural countries"},{"id":1211,"answer":"c. Natural disasters and traditional buildings"},{"id":1212,"answer":"d. Natural disasters and industrial countries"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":285,"quiz_id":25,"question":"3. Which would be the best source to learn more about the San Francisco Earthquake of 1906?","answers":[{"id":1213,"answer":"a. A personal website by someone who currently resides in San Francisco."},{"id":1214,"answer":"b. A journal written by someone who survived the 1906 earthquake."},{"id":1215,"answer":"c. An atlas showing the epicenter of the 1906 quake."},{"id":1216,"answer":"d. An online encyclopedia entry about earthquakes."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":286,"quiz_id":25,"question":"4. Another word for the underlined word \"vast\" in the passage is......","answers":[{"id":1217,"answer":"a. extensive"},{"id":1218,"answer":"b. miniature"},{"id":1219,"answer":"c. simultaneous"},{"id":1220,"answer":"d. perpetual"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":287,"quiz_id":25,"question":"5. After reading the passage, which sentence is correct about the 1906 earthquake?","answers":[{"id":1221,"answer":"a. Flooding was a huge problem after the earthquake."},{"id":1222,"answer":"b. The earthquake left everyone in the city without shelter."},{"id":1223,"answer":"c. People were ill-prepared for any type of disaster in the 1900s."},{"id":1224,"answer":"d. The fires after the earthquake caused major damage to San Francisco."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":288,"quiz_id":25,"question":"6. Deliberate design and planning began ......................","answers":[{"id":1225,"answer":"a. before 1900s"},{"id":1226,"answer":"b. exactly in 1900s"},{"id":1227,"answer":"c. many years after 1900s"},{"id":1228,"answer":"d. 1900 years ago"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":289,"quiz_id":25,"question":"7. According to the information in the passage, what do you think will happen if an earthquake hits San Francisco these days?","answers":[{"id":1229,"answer":"a. The city will be less prepared than in 1906"},{"id":1230,"answer":"b. Fires will ravage the city after an earthquake."},{"id":1231,"answer":"c. The city will be better prepared for it."},{"id":1232,"answer":"d. The citizens will refuse to rebuild the city."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":290,"quiz_id":25,"question":"8. Nowadays, buildings in developed countries are designed to..............various, unexpected natural disasters.","answers":[{"id":1233,"answer":"a. resist"},{"id":1234,"answer":"b. assist"},{"id":1235,"answer":"c. insist"},{"id":1236,"answer":"d. consist"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2}]}]}}
/// message : ""

class QuizModel {
  QuizModel({
      this.success, 
      this.data, 
      this.message,});

  QuizModel.fromJson(dynamic json) {
    success = json['success'];
    data = json['data'] != null ? Data.fromJson(json['data']) : null;
    message = json['message'];
  }
  bool? success;
  Data? data;
  String? message;

  Map<String, dynamic> toJson() {
    final map = <String, dynamic>{};
    map['success'] = success;
    if (data != null) {
      map['data'] = data?.toJson();
    }
    map['message'] = message;
    return map;
  }

}

/// attempt : {"attempt_id":726,"student_id":2,"started_at":"20:56:10"}
/// quiz : {"id":25,"title":"امتحان المحاضره السادسة (Comprehension)","description":"<div class=\"exam-alert\">\r\n<h3>❗ تنبيهات مهمة:</h3>\r\n<ul>\r\n<li>لا تقم بتحديث الصفحة أو إغلاقها أثناء أداء الامتحان، لأن هذا قد يؤدي إلى فقدان إجاباتك أو إنهاء المحاولة تلقائيًا.</li>\r\n<li>سيتم إغلاق الامتحان تلقائيًا بعد انتهاء الوقت المحدد، ولن تتمكن من إرسال إجاباتك بعد ذلك.</li>\r\n<li>لا تستخدم أكثر من جهاز أو أكثر من نافذة/لسان (Tab) للامتحان، فقد يؤدي ذلك إلى فقدان البيانات أو حظر المحاولة.</li>\r\n<li>تأكد من أن اتصال الإنترنت مستقر قبل البدء.</li>\r\n<li>بعد الضغط على زر \"إرسال\"، لا تغادر الصفحة حتى تظهر لك رسالة التأكيد بنجاح إرسال الامتحان.</li>\r\n<li>في حالة وجود مشكلة تقنية أثناء الامتحان، يرجى التواصل فورًا مع الدعم الفني.</li>\r\n</ul>\r\n</div>","course_id":4,"have_duration":true,"duration_minutes":16,"attempt_count":100,"remaining_attempts":76,"full_score":16,"question_count":8,"questions":[{"type":"reading_passage","id":3,"description":"<p class=\"MsoNormal\" style=\"margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; line-height: 15.6933px; font-size: 11pt; font-family: Calibri, sans-serif; text-align: center;\" align=\"center\"><strong><u><span dir=\"RTL\" lang=\"AR-SA\" style=\"font-size: 18pt; line-height: 25.68px; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif;\">&nbsp;</span></u></strong></p>\r\n<p class=\"MsoNormal\" style=\"margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; line-height: 15.6933px; font-size: 11pt; font-family: Calibri, sans-serif;\"><strong><span style=\"font-size: 14pt; line-height: 19.9733px; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif;\">Read the following passage, then answer the questions: Today, in most industrialized countries in the world, buildings are designed to withstand various, unexpected natural disasters. Safety measures are installed in modern-day designs to help contain the spread of fire, and design engineers make sure newer structures are deliberately planned to hold against the violent shifting of the earth during an unexpected earthquake. However, such deliberate design and planning was not the case during the early 1900s. On April 18, 1906, in the morning hours of the day, the citizens of San Francisco, California, were witnesses to an earthquake so monumental. The tremors were felt as far north as Oregon. Neither the city nor its people were prepared for what would happen next: the devastation of their city. The actual earthquake only lasted two minutes. Of course, the violent tremors must have seemed much longer to the actual eyewitnesses, but the fires that came after the earthquake lasted for nearly three days. The enormous loss from the disaster included the lives of at least five hundred people, and an estimated three thousand acres of the city were destroyed. This disaster is often called simply the \"Great Quake\" because of the vast destruction that occurred.</span></strong></p>","questions":[{"id":283,"quiz_id":25,"question":"1. The best sentence that can summarize the last paragraph is...........................","answers":[{"id":1205,"answer":"a. The kinds of earthquakes that happened in San Francisco"},{"id":1206,"answer":"b. The duration and the effects of San Francisco earthquake"},{"id":1207,"answer":"c. The preparation the citizens of San Francisco made to face the earthquake"},{"id":1208,"answer":"d. The government stands with its citizens together to encounter the earthquake."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":284,"quiz_id":25,"question":"2. The best title for the passage is...............","answers":[{"id":1209,"answer":"a. New buildings can face natural disasters"},{"id":1210,"answer":"b. New buildings are designed by natural countries"},{"id":1211,"answer":"c. Natural disasters and traditional buildings"},{"id":1212,"answer":"d. Natural disasters and industrial countries"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":285,"quiz_id":25,"question":"3. Which would be the best source to learn more about the San Francisco Earthquake of 1906?","answers":[{"id":1213,"answer":"a. A personal website by someone who currently resides in San Francisco."},{"id":1214,"answer":"b. A journal written by someone who survived the 1906 earthquake."},{"id":1215,"answer":"c. An atlas showing the epicenter of the 1906 quake."},{"id":1216,"answer":"d. An online encyclopedia entry about earthquakes."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":286,"quiz_id":25,"question":"4. Another word for the underlined word \"vast\" in the passage is......","answers":[{"id":1217,"answer":"a. extensive"},{"id":1218,"answer":"b. miniature"},{"id":1219,"answer":"c. simultaneous"},{"id":1220,"answer":"d. perpetual"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":287,"quiz_id":25,"question":"5. After reading the passage, which sentence is correct about the 1906 earthquake?","answers":[{"id":1221,"answer":"a. Flooding was a huge problem after the earthquake."},{"id":1222,"answer":"b. The earthquake left everyone in the city without shelter."},{"id":1223,"answer":"c. People were ill-prepared for any type of disaster in the 1900s."},{"id":1224,"answer":"d. The fires after the earthquake caused major damage to San Francisco."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":288,"quiz_id":25,"question":"6. Deliberate design and planning began ......................","answers":[{"id":1225,"answer":"a. before 1900s"},{"id":1226,"answer":"b. exactly in 1900s"},{"id":1227,"answer":"c. many years after 1900s"},{"id":1228,"answer":"d. 1900 years ago"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":289,"quiz_id":25,"question":"7. According to the information in the passage, what do you think will happen if an earthquake hits San Francisco these days?","answers":[{"id":1229,"answer":"a. The city will be less prepared than in 1906"},{"id":1230,"answer":"b. Fires will ravage the city after an earthquake."},{"id":1231,"answer":"c. The city will be better prepared for it."},{"id":1232,"answer":"d. The citizens will refuse to rebuild the city."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":290,"quiz_id":25,"question":"8. Nowadays, buildings in developed countries are designed to..............various, unexpected natural disasters.","answers":[{"id":1233,"answer":"a. resist"},{"id":1234,"answer":"b. assist"},{"id":1235,"answer":"c. insist"},{"id":1236,"answer":"d. consist"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2}]}]}

class Data {
  Data({
      this.attempt, 
      this.quiz,});

  Data.fromJson(dynamic json) {
    attempt = json['attempt'] != null ? Attempt.fromJson(json['attempt']) : null;
    quiz = json['quiz'] != null ? Quiz.fromJson(json['quiz']) : null;
  }
  Attempt? attempt;
  Quiz? quiz;

  Map<String, dynamic> toJson() {
    final map = <String, dynamic>{};
    if (attempt != null) {
      map['attempt'] = attempt?.toJson();
    }
    if (quiz != null) {
      map['quiz'] = quiz?.toJson();
    }
    return map;
  }

}

/// id : 25
/// title : "امتحان المحاضره السادسة (Comprehension)"
/// description : "<div class=\"exam-alert\">\r\n<h3>❗ تنبيهات مهمة:</h3>\r\n<ul>\r\n<li>لا تقم بتحديث الصفحة أو إغلاقها أثناء أداء الامتحان، لأن هذا قد يؤدي إلى فقدان إجاباتك أو إنهاء المحاولة تلقائيًا.</li>\r\n<li>سيتم إغلاق الامتحان تلقائيًا بعد انتهاء الوقت المحدد، ولن تتمكن من إرسال إجاباتك بعد ذلك.</li>\r\n<li>لا تستخدم أكثر من جهاز أو أكثر من نافذة/لسان (Tab) للامتحان، فقد يؤدي ذلك إلى فقدان البيانات أو حظر المحاولة.</li>\r\n<li>تأكد من أن اتصال الإنترنت مستقر قبل البدء.</li>\r\n<li>بعد الضغط على زر \"إرسال\"، لا تغادر الصفحة حتى تظهر لك رسالة التأكيد بنجاح إرسال الامتحان.</li>\r\n<li>في حالة وجود مشكلة تقنية أثناء الامتحان، يرجى التواصل فورًا مع الدعم الفني.</li>\r\n</ul>\r\n</div>"
/// course_id : 4
/// have_duration : true
/// duration_minutes : 16
/// attempt_count : 100
/// remaining_attempts : 76
/// full_score : 16
/// question_count : 8
/// questions : [{"type":"reading_passage","id":3,"description":"<p class=\"MsoNormal\" style=\"margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; line-height: 15.6933px; font-size: 11pt; font-family: Calibri, sans-serif; text-align: center;\" align=\"center\"><strong><u><span dir=\"RTL\" lang=\"AR-SA\" style=\"font-size: 18pt; line-height: 25.68px; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif;\">&nbsp;</span></u></strong></p>\r\n<p class=\"MsoNormal\" style=\"margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; line-height: 15.6933px; font-size: 11pt; font-family: Calibri, sans-serif;\"><strong><span style=\"font-size: 14pt; line-height: 19.9733px; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif;\">Read the following passage, then answer the questions: Today, in most industrialized countries in the world, buildings are designed to withstand various, unexpected natural disasters. Safety measures are installed in modern-day designs to help contain the spread of fire, and design engineers make sure newer structures are deliberately planned to hold against the violent shifting of the earth during an unexpected earthquake. However, such deliberate design and planning was not the case during the early 1900s. On April 18, 1906, in the morning hours of the day, the citizens of San Francisco, California, were witnesses to an earthquake so monumental. The tremors were felt as far north as Oregon. Neither the city nor its people were prepared for what would happen next: the devastation of their city. The actual earthquake only lasted two minutes. Of course, the violent tremors must have seemed much longer to the actual eyewitnesses, but the fires that came after the earthquake lasted for nearly three days. The enormous loss from the disaster included the lives of at least five hundred people, and an estimated three thousand acres of the city were destroyed. This disaster is often called simply the \"Great Quake\" because of the vast destruction that occurred.</span></strong></p>","questions":[{"id":283,"quiz_id":25,"question":"1. The best sentence that can summarize the last paragraph is...........................","answers":[{"id":1205,"answer":"a. The kinds of earthquakes that happened in San Francisco"},{"id":1206,"answer":"b. The duration and the effects of San Francisco earthquake"},{"id":1207,"answer":"c. The preparation the citizens of San Francisco made to face the earthquake"},{"id":1208,"answer":"d. The government stands with its citizens together to encounter the earthquake."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":284,"quiz_id":25,"question":"2. The best title for the passage is...............","answers":[{"id":1209,"answer":"a. New buildings can face natural disasters"},{"id":1210,"answer":"b. New buildings are designed by natural countries"},{"id":1211,"answer":"c. Natural disasters and traditional buildings"},{"id":1212,"answer":"d. Natural disasters and industrial countries"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":285,"quiz_id":25,"question":"3. Which would be the best source to learn more about the San Francisco Earthquake of 1906?","answers":[{"id":1213,"answer":"a. A personal website by someone who currently resides in San Francisco."},{"id":1214,"answer":"b. A journal written by someone who survived the 1906 earthquake."},{"id":1215,"answer":"c. An atlas showing the epicenter of the 1906 quake."},{"id":1216,"answer":"d. An online encyclopedia entry about earthquakes."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":286,"quiz_id":25,"question":"4. Another word for the underlined word \"vast\" in the passage is......","answers":[{"id":1217,"answer":"a. extensive"},{"id":1218,"answer":"b. miniature"},{"id":1219,"answer":"c. simultaneous"},{"id":1220,"answer":"d. perpetual"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":287,"quiz_id":25,"question":"5. After reading the passage, which sentence is correct about the 1906 earthquake?","answers":[{"id":1221,"answer":"a. Flooding was a huge problem after the earthquake."},{"id":1222,"answer":"b. The earthquake left everyone in the city without shelter."},{"id":1223,"answer":"c. People were ill-prepared for any type of disaster in the 1900s."},{"id":1224,"answer":"d. The fires after the earthquake caused major damage to San Francisco."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":288,"quiz_id":25,"question":"6. Deliberate design and planning began ......................","answers":[{"id":1225,"answer":"a. before 1900s"},{"id":1226,"answer":"b. exactly in 1900s"},{"id":1227,"answer":"c. many years after 1900s"},{"id":1228,"answer":"d. 1900 years ago"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":289,"quiz_id":25,"question":"7. According to the information in the passage, what do you think will happen if an earthquake hits San Francisco these days?","answers":[{"id":1229,"answer":"a. The city will be less prepared than in 1906"},{"id":1230,"answer":"b. Fires will ravage the city after an earthquake."},{"id":1231,"answer":"c. The city will be better prepared for it."},{"id":1232,"answer":"d. The citizens will refuse to rebuild the city."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":290,"quiz_id":25,"question":"8. Nowadays, buildings in developed countries are designed to..............various, unexpected natural disasters.","answers":[{"id":1233,"answer":"a. resist"},{"id":1234,"answer":"b. assist"},{"id":1235,"answer":"c. insist"},{"id":1236,"answer":"d. consist"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2}]}]

class Quiz {
  Quiz({
      this.id, 
      this.title, 
      this.description, 
      this.courseId, 
      this.haveDuration, 
      this.durationMinutes, 
      this.attemptCount, 
      this.remainingAttempts, 
      this.fullScore, 
      this.questionCount, 
      this.questions,});

  Quiz.fromJson(dynamic json) {
    id = json['id'];
    title = json['title'];
    description = json['description'];
    courseId = json['course_id'];
    haveDuration = json['have_duration'];
    durationMinutes = json['duration_minutes'];
    attemptCount = json['attempt_count'];
    remainingAttempts = json['remaining_attempts'];
    fullScore = json['full_score'];
    questionCount = json['question_count'];
    if (json['questions'] != null) {
      questions = [];
      json['questions'].forEach((v) {
        questions?.add(Questions.fromJson(v));
      });
    }
  }
  int? id;
  String? title;
  String? description;
  int? courseId;
  bool? haveDuration;
  int? durationMinutes;
  int? attemptCount;
  int? remainingAttempts;
  int? fullScore;
  int? questionCount;
  List<Questions>? questions;

  Map<String, dynamic> toJson() {
    final map = <String, dynamic>{};
    map['id'] = id;
    map['title'] = title;
    map['description'] = description;
    map['course_id'] = courseId;
    map['have_duration'] = haveDuration;
    map['duration_minutes'] = durationMinutes;
    map['attempt_count'] = attemptCount;
    map['remaining_attempts'] = remainingAttempts;
    map['full_score'] = fullScore;
    map['question_count'] = questionCount;
    if (questions != null) {
      map['questions'] = questions?.map((v) => v.toJson()).toList();
    }
    return map;
  }

}

/// type : "reading_passage"
/// id : 3
/// description : "<p class=\"MsoNormal\" style=\"margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; line-height: 15.6933px; font-size: 11pt; font-family: Calibri, sans-serif; text-align: center;\" align=\"center\"><strong><u><span dir=\"RTL\" lang=\"AR-SA\" style=\"font-size: 18pt; line-height: 25.68px; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif;\">&nbsp;</span></u></strong></p>\r\n<p class=\"MsoNormal\" style=\"margin: 0cm 0cm 0.0001pt; line-height: 15.6933px; font-size: 11pt; font-family: Calibri, sans-serif;\"><strong><span style=\"font-size: 14pt; line-height: 19.9733px; font-family: 'Times New Roman', serif;\">Read the following passage, then answer the questions: Today, in most industrialized countries in the world, buildings are designed to withstand various, unexpected natural disasters. Safety measures are installed in modern-day designs to help contain the spread of fire, and design engineers make sure newer structures are deliberately planned to hold against the violent shifting of the earth during an unexpected earthquake. However, such deliberate design and planning was not the case during the early 1900s. On April 18, 1906, in the morning hours of the day, the citizens of San Francisco, California, were witnesses to an earthquake so monumental. The tremors were felt as far north as Oregon. Neither the city nor its people were prepared for what would happen next: the devastation of their city. The actual earthquake only lasted two minutes. Of course, the violent tremors must have seemed much longer to the actual eyewitnesses, but the fires that came after the earthquake lasted for nearly three days. The enormous loss from the disaster included the lives of at least five hundred people, and an estimated three thousand acres of the city were destroyed. This disaster is often called simply the \"Great Quake\" because of the vast destruction that occurred.</span></strong></p>"
/// questions : [{"id":283,"quiz_id":25,"question":"1. The best sentence that can summarize the last paragraph is...........................","answers":[{"id":1205,"answer":"a. The kinds of earthquakes that happened in San Francisco"},{"id":1206,"answer":"b. The duration and the effects of San Francisco earthquake"},{"id":1207,"answer":"c. The preparation the citizens of San Francisco made to face the earthquake"},{"id":1208,"answer":"d. The government stands with its citizens together to encounter the earthquake."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":284,"quiz_id":25,"question":"2. The best title for the passage is...............","answers":[{"id":1209,"answer":"a. New buildings can face natural disasters"},{"id":1210,"answer":"b. New buildings are designed by natural countries"},{"id":1211,"answer":"c. Natural disasters and traditional buildings"},{"id":1212,"answer":"d. Natural disasters and industrial countries"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":285,"quiz_id":25,"question":"3. Which would be the best source to learn more about the San Francisco Earthquake of 1906?","answers":[{"id":1213,"answer":"a. A personal website by someone who currently resides in San Francisco."},{"id":1214,"answer":"b. A journal written by someone who survived the 1906 earthquake."},{"id":1215,"answer":"c. An atlas showing the epicenter of the 1906 quake."},{"id":1216,"answer":"d. An online encyclopedia entry about earthquakes."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":286,"quiz_id":25,"question":"4. Another word for the underlined word \"vast\" in the passage is......","answers":[{"id":1217,"answer":"a. extensive"},{"id":1218,"answer":"b. miniature"},{"id":1219,"answer":"c. simultaneous"},{"id":1220,"answer":"d. perpetual"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":287,"quiz_id":25,"question":"5. After reading the passage, which sentence is correct about the 1906 earthquake?","answers":[{"id":1221,"answer":"a. Flooding was a huge problem after the earthquake."},{"id":1222,"answer":"b. The earthquake left everyone in the city without shelter."},{"id":1223,"answer":"c. People were ill-prepared for any type of disaster in the 1900s."},{"id":1224,"answer":"d. The fires after the earthquake caused major damage to San Francisco."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":288,"quiz_id":25,"question":"6. Deliberate design and planning began ......................","answers":[{"id":1225,"answer":"a. before 1900s"},{"id":1226,"answer":"b. exactly in 1900s"},{"id":1227,"answer":"c. many years after 1900s"},{"id":1228,"answer":"d. 1900 years ago"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":289,"quiz_id":25,"question":"7. According to the information in the passage, what do you think will happen if an earthquake hits San Francisco these days?","answers":[{"id":1229,"answer":"a. The city will be less prepared than in 1906"},{"id":1230,"answer":"b. Fires will ravage the city after an earthquake."},{"id":1231,"answer":"c. The city will be better prepared for it."},{"id":1232,"answer":"d. The citizens will refuse to rebuild the city."}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2},{"id":290,"quiz_id":25,"question":"8. Nowadays, buildings in developed countries are designed to..............various, unexpected natural disasters.","answers":[{"id":1233,"answer":"a. resist"},{"id":1234,"answer":"b. assist"},{"id":1235,"answer":"c. insist"},{"id":1236,"answer":"d. consist"}],"expected_answer":null,"type":"multiple_choice","points":2}]

class Questions {
  Questions({
      this.type, 
      this.id, 
      this.description, 
      this.questions,});

  Questions.fromJson(dynamic json) {
    type = json['type'];
    id = json['id'];
    description = json['description'];
    if (json['questions'] != null) {
      questions = [];
      json['questions'].forEach((v) {
        questions?.add(Questions.fromJson(v));
      });
    }
  }
  String? type;
  int? id;
  String? description;
  List<Questions>? questions;

  Map<String, dynamic> toJson() {
    final map = <String, dynamic>{};
    map['type'] = type;
    map['id'] = id;
    map['description'] = description;
    if (questions != null) {
      map['questions'] = questions?.map((v) => v.toJson()).toList();
    }
    return map;
  }

}

/// id : 283
/// quiz_id : 25
/// question : "1. The best sentence that can summarize the last paragraph is..........................."
/// answers : [{"id":1205,"answer":"a. The kinds of earthquakes that happened in San Francisco"},{"id":1206,"answer":"b. The duration and the effects of San Francisco earthquake"},{"id":1207,"answer":"c. The preparation the citizens of San Francisco made to face the earthquake"},{"id":1208,"answer":"d. The government stands with its citizens together to encounter the earthquake."}]
/// expected_answer : null
/// type : "multiple_choice"
/// points : 2

class Question {
  Question({
      this.id, 
      this.quizId, 
      this.question, 
      this.answers, 
      this.expectedAnswer, 
      this.type, 
      this.points,});

  Question.fromJson(dynamic json) {
    id = json['id'];
    quizId = json['quiz_id'];
    question = json['question'];
    if (json['answers'] != null) {
      answers = [];
      json['answers'].forEach((v) {
        answers?.add(Answers.fromJson(v));
      });
    }
    expectedAnswer = json['expected_answer'];
    type = json['type'];
    points = json['points'];
  }
  int? id;
  int? quizId;
  String? question;
  List<Answers>? answers;
  dynamic expectedAnswer;
  String? type;
  int? points;

  Map<String, dynamic> toJson() {
    final map = <String, dynamic>{};
    map['id'] = id;
    map['quiz_id'] = quizId;
    map['question'] = question;
    if (answers != null) {
      map['answers'] = answers?.map((v) => v.toJson()).toList();
    }
    map['expected_answer'] = expectedAnswer;
    map['type'] = type;
    map['points'] = points;
    return map;
  }

}

/// id : 1205
/// answer : "a. The kinds of earthquakes that happened in San Francisco"

class Answers {
  Answers({
      this.id, 
      this.answer,});

  Answers.fromJson(dynamic json) {
    id = json['id'];
    answer = json['answer'];
  }
  int? id;
  String? answer;

  Map<String, dynamic> toJson() {
    final map = <String, dynamic>{};
    map['id'] = id;
    map['answer'] = answer;
    return map;
  }

}

/// attempt_id : 726
/// student_id : 2
/// started_at : "20:56:10"

class Attempt {
  Attempt({
      this.attemptId, 
      this.studentId, 
      this.startedAt,});

  Attempt.fromJson(dynamic json) {
    attemptId = json['attempt_id'];
    studentId = json['student_id'];
    startedAt = json['started_at'];
  }
  int? attemptId;
  int? studentId;
  String? startedAt;

  Map<String, dynamic> toJson() {
    final map = <String, dynamic>{};
    map['attempt_id'] = attemptId;
    map['student_id'] = studentId;
    map['started_at'] = startedAt;
    return map;
  }

}